twinpinenetwork.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy policy - Twinpine

LAST UPDATED on 5th JANUARY, 2017

Twinpine (“ **Twinpine** ”, “ **we** ”, or “ **our** ”) values the privacy of our users, members, and others who visit and use our website www.Twinpinenetwork.com our Software Development Kit (“SDK”), the Twinpine publisher platform and”) (collectively or individually “ **Users** ” or “ **you** “). The Twinpine site contains information regarding a variety of services offered by Twinpine (collectively the “ **Service** ”). This Privacy Policy governs information you provide to us or that we learn from your use of the Twinpine site, and tells you how we may collect, use, and share this information.

Twinpine complies with the applicable Laws which are in force in the Federal Republic of Nigeria regarding the collection, use, and, retention of personal data from users. Twinpine certifies that it adheres to those laws on notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. 

**The Information Twinpine Collects**

**User Provided Information:**  When registering for an account or expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about Twinpine or its Service, you may provide “personal information,” such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, credit card number, and other billing information as needed. In addition, Twinpine may give you the option to provide us with certain information about your business.

**Cookies Information:**  When you visit the Twinpine site, we use cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to personalize your experience on the Twinpine site. Twinpine may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. Persistent cookies, unlike session cookies, remain after you close your browser, and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Twinpine site.  Using persistent cookies, we can “remember” what you have done on the Twinpine site previously and personalize our Site for you. Cookies may be disabled through your browser settings. Please note that disabling cookies may prevent you from accessing some of the Twinpine’s site functionalities and offerings.

**Automatically Collected Information:**  When you visit the Twinpine Site or open one of our HTML emails, we may record certain information from your browser through clear gifs/web beacons or similar technologies. This “automatically collected” information may include your Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or after the Twinpine site, the pages you view on our Site, and the dates and times that you visit.

**Opting-out:** You can “Opt-out” from having cookies stored on your PC when ads are shown from the Twinpine Ad Serving system. To “Opt-out” click the button below 

**The Way Twinpine Uses Information**

Twinpine uses the collected information:

  * to provide and improve the Twinpine Site and Service;
  * to fulfill your requests regarding the Twinpine Site and/or the Service; and
  * To send you newsletters, and to contact you about special offers, new products, and services.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, please click the “Unsubscribe” link within the email, access the email preferences in your account settings, or contact us at [support@twinpine.com](mailto:support@twinpine.com). We will also use your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes, such as notifying you of major Site and Service updates.

Twinpine may use all of the information that we collect from our Users:

  * to understand the usage trends and preferences;
  * to improve the Twinpine Site and Service’s appearance, features, and functionality; and
  * To improve our marketing and promotional efforts.

**When Twinpine Discloses Information**

Twinpine may disclose both personally identifiable and automatically collected information to affiliated companies, service providers, or other businesses or persons to:

  * process such information on our behalf;
  * to perform website maintenance and security functions; and
  * to improve the appearance, features, and functionality of the Twinpine Site and Service.

We use reasonable efforts to: (i) see that these parties process such information in compliance with our [Privacy Policy](https://www.twinpinenetwork.com/privacy-policy/), (ii) limit their use of such information to the extent necessary to provide these services to us, and (iii) see that these parties use appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We may also share automatically collected and other aggregated, non-personally-identifiable information with third parties to understand the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Service and the Twinpine Site.

Except as otherwise noted in this [Privacy Policy](https://www.twinpinenetwork.com/privacy-policy/), Twinpine does not share personal information about Users with third parties unless doing so is appropriate to carry out a User’s request; is legally required; or Twinpine reasonably believes such disclosure is necessary to protect Twinpine’s property, other legal rights, or the rights or property of others. We do not share your personal information with other third-party organizations for their marketing or promotional use without your consent, or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you have the ability to opt-in.

**User Profile and Password**

You have access to your personal information, and you may update, correct, or delete your member information and email preferences at any time by logging into your account, or by e-mailing Twinpine at support@twinpine.com with your request. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting Users profile access. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.

**Children**

We cannot prohibit minors from visiting the Site. We must rely on parents, guardians and those responsible for supervising children younger than 15 to decide which materials are appropriate for such children to view and/or purchase.

We take special steps to safeguard the privacy of children and if you are under 15 years of age, you may browse our Site. However, you may not provide personal information to us. For example, you cannot register or make a purchase. This Site is not designed for children and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any children under 15.

**Third Party Advertisers and Links to Other Sites**

Twinpine allows third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements within the Twinpine Site. These third parties may send, directly to your browser, advertisements and links that appear within the Twinpine Site. They may automatically receive your IP Address when this happens, and use certain tracking technologies (such as, but not limited to, cookies, JavaScript, and/or web beacons), which track your browsing activities and interests, to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, and personalize their advertising content.

Twinpine does not provide any of your personal information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent, or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you have the ability to opt-in. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Twinpine to show an advertisement to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they were trying to reach. 

Twinpine’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. Please consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. You can help to ensure the security of your information by taking simple precautions such as preventing unauthorized access to your login information, and sign off of your account when you are finished using your computer.

If Twinpine learns of a security systems breach, we may attempt to notify you via the most recent email address we have on file, or post a notice on the Twinpine Site. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive a security breach notice in writing. To receive a free, written, security breach notice (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice), please contact us at [support@twinpinenetwork.com](mailto:support@twinpinenetwork.com)

**In the Event of Merger or Sale**

If Twinpine should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets or stock sold to or merged with another entity, the information Twinpine receives from you through the Twinpine Site is a Twinpine asset and may be transferred to any such entity. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Site of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Changes and Updates to this  **[ **Privacy Policy**](https://www.twinpinenetwork.com/privacy-policy/)

We may occasionally update this [Privacy Policy](https://www.twinpinenetwork.com/privacy-policy/) to reflect changes to our privacy practices. The amended [Privacy Policy](https://www.twinpinenetwork.com/privacy-policy/) will be displayed on our Site. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by means of a notice on the Twinpine Site, prior to the changes becoming effective. Please check our [Privacy Policy](https://www.twinpinenetwork.com/privacy-policy/) regularly to ensure you have read the latest version and to stay informed of our privacy practices. Your continued use of the Twinpine Site constitutes your agreement to this [Privacy Policy](https://www.twinpinenetwork.com/privacy-policy/) and any updates.

**Contacting Twinpine**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this [Privacy Policy](mailto:support@twinpinenetwork.com), please email us at [support@twinpine.com](mailto:support@twinpinenetwork.com)

**Twinpine limited**  
98A Island Way , Dolphin Estate

Ikoyi, Lagos

**TEL NO**

+234 1400 00029
